Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Advertise your product or brand here
contact @ subs4free.info today
Subtitles by explosiveskull
@ subs4free.info
- What took you so long?
- Fish Mitten's. Where is she?
Fish Mitten's.
- What'd you do to her?
- Nothin'.
There could've been, uh,
rat poison in that garbage.
That could've been it.
This fucking dog, Traylor,
I told you about them.
Now I gotta
pick all this shit up.
Shhh.
Sorry, girl.
Shit.
What I wouldn't do
to shoot my ex's dog.
Have you met my ex?
You're a little early.
- Early for what?
- You didn't talk to Doris?
She's just getting in now.
She might've called my place,
but I wasn't home.
What she's supposed to be
telling me?
Joseph got picked up
this morning.
They got him in town, and they said
they'll only release him to you.
Jesus Christ.
You think this is us?
Just shitty parents?
I think he thinks
his dad is a fuck-up.
And it gives him a free pass.
I'll meet you there at noon.
No reason to get him out early.
Hey.
Have you seen Harley?
No.
I'll keep an eye out for her.
Dispatch?
Doris?
I'm here, Chief.
I've been calling your place all morning.
I'm at Joss's.
Oh, yeah?
Not like that. Get on with it.
Skip the hillbilly antics
and just give me the highlights.
I'm just trying
to get organized.
Today has been crazy,
really crazy.
Burner called earlier.
He said some drunk white guy
was trying to eat his chickens,
and that if you didn't show up
soon,
he was gonna blow
his fucking head off.
His words, Chief.
Where's Bumper?
Where else, Chief?
He's in the woods.
Bring him down and get him strapped.
What else?
You know
Joseph got picked up?
I talked to Joss already.
I'll get him this afternoon.
That's not what I was gonna
mention, Chief.
Spit it out.
Lysol got picked up with him.
Of course he did.
This band is open.
Keep me posted.
One more thing, Chief.
Your dad called.
He sounded... scared.
Dad?
Look inside!
Look inside.
Dead salmon.
I think I'm going crazy.
Dad, you...
That... that thing is gutted!
I pulled him out of the river
this morning.
I've been fishing these rivers
for 60 years,
I never seen nothing like that.
I have gas in the trunk.
Burn it.
What the fuck is going on, Dad?
Give me the gas and the dog.
Feel like coming out
of retirement?
You're a Deputy in the Red Crow
Police Department.
Bumper will be up at his camp.
Bring him down.
See what's up at Burner's.
Don't get anyone shot.
That fish is still moving.
Fuck.
Fuck...
So you want
to quit drinking, just...
fuck AA,
just lock somebody in a cell
with you two fucking idiots
all night.
Hey, fucking die already,
hillbilly.
You here to break me out?
- Come on, man.
- Hmm.
I knew Dad wouldn't come and get
you, but he'd come get us.
- Hmm.
- So I got arrested townie side.
Ooh, do you think he's gonna come get you?
He could just leave you.
My mom wouldn't let him.
Thanks, man, but...
I'm no fucking charity case,
and you being
Traylor's good son,
any stupid shit you do,
your people are gonna hang on me.
Maybe I'm just trying to fuck
with my dad, then.
That's the same difference,
Joey.
Whoa!
Oh, my fuck!
Yo!
Get us outta here!!
Jesus, Traylor,
you said noon,
and that was an hour ago.
Get the hell off RC time.
I'm here.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hey, Sham.
Whenever you're ready, man.
We don't got all day.
Traylor.
Hey, Joss.
So we got some paperwork for you
to read and sign, and then, uh...
me and Traylor here, I guess we'll just
do that all up just like last time.
You know your boy gets arrested
more than a prostitute?
I'll be in the car.
She seems mad.
So what'd he do?
Well, we caught him
on the bridge.
He had climbed up the structure
and...
and shimmied over the road
on the crossbar.
And then he took a shit
on the first car that drove by.
Happens there was a little lady
from our side of the line.
She probably thought it was a
goddamn pterodactyl shitting on her.
Gross. Alright. Ahem.
Let's go.
It smells like a fucking ass
in here!
What's with the blood?
Was this guy beat up
when he came in?
No, he's been clutching his guts
all night. And then he started...
Come on.
Don't go nowhere, shitbrains.
What the fuck?! Ah!!
Ah! Help!! Help!
Ow! Ah, fuck! He fucking bit me.
You don't bite me
when I'm fighting, motherfucker!
- Come on.
- Give me that. You want to eat people?!
You want to...
you want to eat people?!
You want to fuckin' eat people,
you cocksucker?!
Hey! Hey!
- Fuckin' lost your goddamn...
- Hey, he's had...
- Now you're going to get your...
- He's had enough!
- ...your fuckin' hillbilly... - That's enough!
- You fucking...
I'll put a new hole
in your head, you sonofabitch!!
You're gonna fuckin' kill him!
Lock 9!!
- Ah!
- Fuck!!
Looks like he got your tit.
Just... just fuck off, or I'll fuckin'
put you back in there, you understand?!
- Fuck.
- This is too fucked up! Where did he go? Where the...
Ah!!
Hey, hey,
you're not leaving me here, right?!
And then this fucking
mental case just lunges, like...
like lunges at Shamu and
bites him right in the chest.
And me and Lysol and Traylor
trying to pull him,
and then he fucking bites me,
too.
I don't give a shit
who bit you.
I'm ready to bite you myself.
So what did you get
arrested for?
Just vandalized some car.
You just vandalized some car?
You need to start
making better choices.
I know I fucked up, Mom.
Now you know?
Well, maybe you do,
maybe you don't.
Look, I know your heart's in the right
place, but... your head's up your ass.
It's not like
I just met Charlie, Mom.
It's not like I don't care
about her.
Look, I really love her.
Look, I'm not talkin'
about Charlie.
I'm talkin' about your brother.
And I'm talkin' about why you keep
getting into trouble with this guy.
He doesn't have anyone else.
Traylor fucking abandoned him.
The whole reserve knows
what happened to his mom.
I hear you and I...
I get you on that.
Joseph, if you're more focused on being
a brother to Lysol than being a father...
...and if the question ever
came up if you were ready...
...the way you're prioritizing
your life right now is your answer.
Well,
that was really fucked up.
This whole day
has been fucked up.
Oh, I'm sure you've had worse.
You on, Chief?
What news?
Shooker called and said
his girlfriend is sick,
and the ambulance from town
still isn't picking up.
They never pick up.
What time did he call you?
And how long has he been
calling the townies?
Well, he called here
at 12:30 this afternoon,
and he said he's been calling for
an ambulance since last night,
but he could be lying.
You have no idea
how many times
I've been over there
because of his bullshit.
His girlfriend's still pregnant?
Pretty sure, boss.
I can't keep bailing you out,
Alan.
Nobody told you
to bail me out.
Tell that to your brother.
Whatever you think of me...
the kid deserves better.
Better than what?
Either one of us.
Sperm donor!
This is the ugliest
waiting room I've ever seen.
Thanks for stopping by.
I'm sorry.
Everything seems like a
good idea when you're drunk.
Says the teenage boy to
his pregnant teenage girlfriend.
At the abortion place.
I didn't even tell my dad.
Are you embarrassed of me?
- What in the hell happened to your arm?
- Don't change the subject.
I'm not changing the subject.
I just want to know what happened.
Look, some hillbilly bit me
in the drunk tank.
My mom's getting me
a tetanus shot.
I'm not gonna bleed to death
waiting,
so can you please
answer my question?
Are you embarrassed of me?
No. Fuck no.
I'm embarrassed of him.
He's just embarrassing.
You still want to do this?
Lydia, are we, uh...
are we out of tetanus?
How could that be?
Yes, the guys in Emergency
cleared us out.
They said they've been getting
a lot of bites.
This town has lost its mind.
A lot of bites.
You got the wrong number.
What's going on?
Run!!
- Jesus Christ, Shooker!
- She's had it.
What the fuck
are you on about?
There's no... no time.
And where there's supposed
to be little finger nails,
little yellow teeth
are growing out.
Of course, you're high,
you stupid cocksuckin'
fuck-face.
- You should've just called a cab right away.
- I got no more money left.
And nobody's gonna let us into
their house to use their phone!
And they don't like her, huh, Chief?
'Cause she's white!
- Is she alright, at least?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
She's definitely not alright,
Chief.
And I got no more coke here. I don't
want anymore. I don't want anymore.
I swear to God, if you don't
get a hold of yourself,
I'm gonna kick your ass off the
face of this fucking planet!
- Where is she?
- Yeah, yeah, upstairs to the left.
I think I... I-I left it open,
maybe?
Y'know, in the back.
In the back room.
Yeah, upstairs to the left.
She said... she said the...
the baby needed to eat...
- ...with no mouth.
- What?!
There was no mouth.
Are you alright, ma'am?
What hap... What happened?
Holy shit.
Keep her the fuck away from you!!
Come on, man!
Ah!!!
Get her!
- You fucking killed her, man.
- Shut up! - Oh...
Oh, fuck, man...
Fuck.
Doris! Doris! Shooker's hurt!
I'm here, boss. You should
see what your father brought in.
You're gonna shit Frisbees.
Hey, man... Fuck.
You brought me here, man.
Doris, I gotta bring Shooker
to the hospital.
There was supposed to be
a fucking ambulance!
I dropped that girl.
I think I killed her!
Joss is coming over
in an ambulance.
She's talking hysterical,
Chief.
About what?
She's saying...
She's saying don't get bit,
Chief?
Don't get bit.
Tell her I'll be right there.
- Fuck, man!!
- Hold on!
You can let me out here, boss.
Stay put.
We're gonna go get 'em.
Traylor. We have to, Traylor.
He's coming back.
Hey!!
Joseph's still in the back.
The door's stuck!
Charlie,
open the fucking door!
Get the fuck out of here!
Get the fuck off me,
you bitch!
Ah!
New chain.
Just like the dog,
Just like the fish,
The dead
are coming back to life.
Subtle.
Would you check this out?
Found a whole box of these,
and this was the only one
that didn't have blood on it.
Could probably swap a blow job for this.
It's cherry-flavoured.
Fuck, you could get a blow job
from anyone.
It's probably the last
cherry-flavoured powder in the world.
I'm eating this.
Shooker's coming in with
Joseph, Charlie and three boat people.
Everyone, behave.
- Oh, to you who are highly favoured.
- No shit.
Hey, Doris,
that's my little brother,
so I wouldn't harm a hair
on his head.
Three more mouths to feed.
Yay.
Ah, good grief, Charlie Brown.
We know the girl; this guy
and his kid are stragglers.
Hey, I know you too.
We've got two more mouths to feed.
The girl's sick.
Welcome
to our pallet-tive care.
Put her down.
What's going on here?
I haven't done anything wrong.
When you're bring in your sick
here, what's right about it?
My little girl got injured,
that's all.
She needs help. I was told
I could get help here.
Who told you?
Oh, wait a minute.
We could just go back and leave or
use one of the boats. We don't need...
- Hey!
- Charlie, we barely know this guy.
Fuck, Lysol, settle down.
Fuck, you just said it, man.
You don't know this guy.
How do you know
this fuckin' townie
didn't come here
with this refugee Pollyanna act
to plant this infected bitch
right on our doorstep?!
- Here, you brought her here.
- What? - Take this knife,
slide it in her ear
and stir it around.
Do you know what we had to do
to get here?!
No, and I don't give a fuck,
either!
You do it up,
or I'll do it for you!
Jesus.
What if my baby's born sick?
You gonna shoot us too?
I do what I have to do.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Easy, boys.
You broke my dipstick.
You owe me a blow job!
Point that gun at Charlie
again, I'll fuckin' kill you!
Joseph! Alan!
What the fuck are you doing?
Just checking for bites
like you told us to.
Are you gonna fucking open up
the floodgates and let them stay?
Look at you.
Look at all of you.
Get your fuckin' shit together!
What are you doing?
How the fuck do you even keep
arranging this?
We're supposed to be helping people.
That's what I'm doing.
We're not supposed
to be doing anything.
We're supposed to be surviving!
How far gone?
We're gonna have to kill her.
What are you guys talking about?
Speak English.
What about the other two?
Joss can look at them.
Just the girl.
Speak English!!
Your girl's been bit.
She can't come in here.
She'll put everyone in danger.
You should've said something.
I heard that you could cure
bites here.
I should've been honest
about that upfront.
But look, look, he's been bit!
She stopped on her breathing.
Everyone inside.
You need to move away from her.
Go inside.
You're not gonna want
to see it come back.
You're especially not gonna want
to see what he does with that axe.
Gotta make them
take that shit down!
I've never killed a child
before.
It was the dogs
that got my family.
I was sentimental about my dog.
Turns out,
immune to the plague doesn't
mean immune to being eaten alive.
Look, I get it, you're still
feeling bad about Karen,
but look around you.
Everyone here lost somebody.
- Kyra.
- What?
Her name was Kyra.
ZED. That's just ZED,
not some little girl.
It's better to, you know,
not look at them as whatchamacallits,
people.
Are you fucking crazy?
You can't bring that here!
Go. Follow J and Charlie,
the pregnant lady,
into the nurses' station.
And don't forget,
ain't nobody immune here
but us.
So feel safe here.
I'm just gonna ask
you a couple of questions, okay?
So how long
were you out there for?
I lost track of the time.
What did you guys eat
while you were out there?
Did you eat any salmon?
Did you eat any dog?
Anything else?
Are you asking me
if I had to eat people?
Has anyone ever answered yes
to that?
Well, what's your answer?
No.
I haven't eaten any people
or dogs...
or fucking anything!
- Settle down.
- Do you have a bathroom?
One more question.
It's a big one.
Did you get bit?
No.
Hello?
Who's there?
Everything is blocked off.
We got four-man teams
at every blockade.
The roads coming in off of 132,
ain't nothing really to worry about.
Stragglers still stumbling in from
some of the podunk towns on the island.
Pretty old and mangled.
Don't move as fast,
so they've been
pickin' them off easy.
Bodies are starting to pile up
faster than we can bury 'em,
so we might have to spark up those
pyres again, regardless of who sees 'em.
They were getting the same
problem on the bridge.
Says it's been coming in
townie-side nonstop.
We're wasting our ammo trying to keep
them from ramping up the blockade.
Bumper found a way around that
without having to fire a single shot,
or mop up a single body.
The bigger problem than the dead-walking-around
townies, is the live breathing ones.
They're coming across
in almost the same numbers.
Some people in Red Crow
don't like it,
but we got to do right
by survivors.
We've been housing all the
intakes here at the hall.
We've been keeping the boats
that have been coming in,
tied up
by the old man's shanty.
If something happens here,
we get separated,
we meet up at the church.
We got enough space
between here and there
to buy us time
to get on those boats.
We wait this thing out
till winter.
Can hit the towns, clean out the
ZEDzicles and find any other survivors.
Keep reminding people...
moose and deer are clean,
and anything out of the water
is bad meat.
We hunt and trap for food.
That mountain water's clean.
That leaves one thing: gas.
Only thing left
is that gas station
that the Muppets own
on the rez side of 132.
Burner said there's a whole reservoir
there that we haven't even tapped yet.
Shooker's been keeping an eye
on things for us.
They've been bringing girls
up there.
Papa Muppet's been tellin' them if they
give him head, they're gonna be immune.
Either way,
we gotta clean 'em out.
It's... the guy that came
with the girl, Chief.
He killed himself.
Fuck.
Jesus, he couldn't
shoot himself like a normal person.
You need a hand, Chief?
I think going on the run has
made your brother even more mental.
I used to think it was because my
dad had him when he was, like, young.
And was just never
in the picture.
The way his mom died
didn't help.
Sent him to foster care,
and who knows what happened there?
He left an Alan
and came back a Lysol.
Yeah, I forgot
that was his mom.
Gave him a pass
on so much fucking nonsense.
"You still have a mom."
Do you know how many times
he said that shit to me?
It has to stop some time.
You can't just be an asshole.
Yeah, fuck him, then.
But either way...
he was right.
Yeah, he's right.
If that girl flipped
five minutes sooner...
I know it's not the sick little
girls that I'm worried about.
Do you know what we have here,
man?
This might be the last place on
the planet that isn't overrun.
I know. I know, I know.
Then what are you doing?
I'm straight up asking you:
Help me understand
what are you doing?
People look at me here...
...like...
...like my vagina's
Pandora's box.
I have nightmares, Joseph.
This baby eating me
from the inside out.
You're immune, I'm not.
What if this baby isn't either?
I mean, what if it just decides
to eat its way out?
Charlie, my mom's watching you
every day.
People have been doing this shit
since monkeys got off their knuckles.
It's not about the pregnancy,
dumbass.
It's about sitting here and just
waiting for something to happen,
because don't you feel it?
Something's gonna happen.
I trust my mother. She says it's healthy.
It has a healthy heartbeat.
Shooker's baby?
I didn't say that.
Look, Shooker's woman was
a dope addict and so was he.
I didn't want this.
I know.
- But you said it a million times when you were at the hospital.
- No, to fight with you.
Have you thought of any names?
No. Not really.
You?
No.
You don't name things
that eat you.
Jesus, Charlie.
I love you.
He clipped me.
Right.
Well, take your shirt off,
let me have a look.
Here, sit.
Ah.
Ah...
Yeah. Ahem.
You're gonna need stitches.
I don't have any lidocaine, so you're
just gonna have to grit your teeth.
Got any beer?
You did so good by him.
Yeah, well...
you're in there too.
Yeah, the part that gets drunk
and takes shits off of bridges.
Look... he's loyal.
And he's smart.
He's a fighter.
And maybe he didn't split
the atom, but...
...he survived
the end of the world.
You're your father's son,
so is Joseph.
Thank you.
These are all the 302s
I could rustle up.
James got more,
but I can't find her drunk ass.
I don't plan on using 'em.
You should've ran that fool off
the reserve when he was alive.
I thought Rob Muppet
was from here.
Everyone thinks that.
But that family's
not from Red Crow.
Speaking of which,
what about this place?
Some of these fuckers
ain't local.
Never seen a brown person since
their grandparents owned one.
And they outnumber us too.
How long
before it comes to pass
they get tired of being herded
by a bunch of Indians?
We got all their guns.
And they're all too civilized to shit
anyplace that doesn't have a door.
What the fuck are they gonna do?
What the fuck
are they gonna to do?
One of them could come in here
and infect this entire camp!
It takes one, Traylor! And Joseph's
pet townie keeps dragging them in here.
- Hey, fuck you.
- Every one of these motherfuckers is a time bomb!
That's why we have a wall.
Anyone flips in here,
this place
is a fucking shooting gallery.
With fucking Peeky
and Maynard up there,
they couldn't hit water
if they fell out of a boat!
There's about, what,
100 people here?
That's three-plus Gs for every
swinging dick we have!
We don't have enough bullets,
man!
You don't have to reload
a sword.
Fuck this shit.
If you say the rez is clean,
so be it.
It's on you... when these bingo
bunnies go south of cheese.
Get word round, J,
the rez is clean,
we got celebratin' to do.
We party at my place!
I'm taking this gas
for my fucking car!
- Hey!
- Let him go.
- Why?
- Because he's not wrong.
Follow him.
Don't let it get out of hand.
Alright, Dad.
Dad?
It's a brave new world.
Leave them to their parties.
They have their recreation,
and we have ours.
Oh, hey.
Ah... listen,
I'm glad you came, man.
I wanted to tell you
that I shouldn't have
put that gun on your lady
this morning.
I want to say...
your punching me in the face,
just means you're gonna be a good father.
That's the weed talking.
It is, but it isn't.
I felt shitty about it, man.
The thing is, it's just more
about Dad and our bullshit.
It's never gonna change.
It can change.
You don't have to be
a trash dad, Joey.
That shit is optional.
And why do you choose
to be a fucking asshole?
Gimme my fucking joint back.
Did it ever fuckin' dawn on you
that I'm not someone to look up to?
That if you have to get arrested
to spend time with somebody...
...they're just fucking
worthless.
I'm not an asshole
to impress you, Joseph.
I'm just an asshole.
Sad.
Yeah, when you find out
family ain't shit.
I don't think you're shit.
Give it time.
- Whoa!
- Yeah, ah-ha.
This is the last of it.
My man.
Alright.
We're square.
Remember that night before Z day?
A bunch of us got arrested for getting
in a fight down at the Fish Mitten?
It was because
of that chick right there.
Anyway...
...her boyfriend has
a stripper's ass in his face.
Lilith's pissed.
So she is looking
for some payback attention.
And she's drunk enough that...
...she'd be willing to get it
from anyone, man.
Anyone.
Long story short...
I get her home,
and I'm eating her out
and she's gushing, right?
Fucking details
you can spare me, man.
Fucking prig here
all of a sudden.
So the phone rings.
And it's Moon from the club,
saying the boys just got arrested
for fighting this chick's
boyfriend and his buddies.
So I forget about the girl.
I head straight down
to the police station.
I'm not even halfway through
the door before I get arrested.
What for?
Fighting.
- And Shamu is, like:
- If you weren't fighting,
- then why is your face all bloody?
- "If you weren't fighting,
how come your face
is all bloody?"
What?
- Come on, loser.
- Hey, I wasn't fighting!
What are you doing?!
This is bullshit, dude!
That's the most fucked-up,
repugnant shit I've ever heard.
At my age, you done it
on purpose at least once.
If he dies by mistake.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Mm.
Shit.
Hey, Lilith! Lilith.
The earth is an animal.
Living and breathing.
White men don't understand this.
That's why the dead
keep coming back to life.
Not because of God.
Because this planet we're on
is so sick of our shit.
This old, tired, angry animal...
...turned these stupid
fucking white men
into something
she can use again:
fertilizer.
Lysol, what the fuck?
Don't let her finish.
Who says we're immune?
Maybe the earth just forgot
about us.
How many did you say there was
in there again?
More than 10.
Twelve or fifteen, counting the girls.
We're using shotguns?
Traylor is. We're inside.
No fun in there with shotguns.
Don't let any of them get out.
Hey.
A little fucking warning.
Look out.
Whew!
Gisigu?
How many did you get?
Four.
So there could be as many
as six or seven left in here?
Maybe ten.
Fuck.
Check if that genny works.
You throw another G at me,
I want to see it coming.
ZED?
Zed dead.
Fuck you.
Fuck.
Joseph!
What the fuck's going on here,
man?
- Joseph.
- Why didn't we kill that G?
No, you gotta get someone
to sound the alarm.
You gotta get
as many people as you can.
- You get them in that hall!
- Why did we bring that here?
It's obvious now:
it's us or them.
Have you fucking lost it, man?
There is no us or them,
there's only us.
- No.
- Okay? Look.
Just come downstairs, we can fix...
we can fix you up.
The whole world's
fucking dead, man.
You still have a family,
though.
Okay? This can all stop.
Just... just stop.
Just stop.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's ok...
Ah, I have no family.
Get her!
You're gonna get all those dicks
for me, okay?
Run!
Run!!!
Clear out!
Run now!!
Run!
What were you saying to her?
I was telling her a story.
She was scared.
We used to tell it to Joseph,
that story.
It's about his grandfather.
I'm scared, Joss.
We're all here.
This place is safe.
Did you hear that?
Joseph!
Joseph.
What happened?
Lysol.
Everyone stay calm.
There's the other exit.
Wait!
Can we panic now?
We're here.
I'm in the basement with Charlie,
Joseph and eight other survivors.
I don't think
anyone else made it.
What was the headcount
up to last week?
100, 150 townies.
Fuck.
Can your people move?
Not all of them.
Hold tight,
we're coming to get you.
Traylor, hurry the fuck up.
How you want to do this?
Who's got the most meat
on 'em?
No problem.
Oh...
It's bad.
Get on with it.
You ready?
That'll buy us some time,
but there's bound
to be more inside.
Get the truck.
Don't use your gun
unless you have to.
Circle around,
keep the engine running.
Where the fuck were you?!
- Where's Charlie?
- What happened to you?
Where's Charlie? Get Charlie.
Dad, Dad, get Charlie.
Get Charlie.
Get Charlie, get Charlie.
There's a truck outside!
You want to live?! Get on it!
Let's go. Let's go.
- Move your ass!
- Alright, let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Move, move!
I am not getting on
without you!
Shooker! Move!
Go!!
This is some fucking rescue.
This door is not gonna hold.
You're gonna have to make a run for it.
- A run for it?
- You have no choice!
And if I don't make it
out of here...
I want you to tell my grandchild
big stories about me.
On the count of three... run!
Go!!
Now, you're gonna
say it exactly like I told you.
No cute stuff.
Traylor...
...they're killing people
in the church.
Normal... real people.
James and Moon
are just killin' 'em.
And I'm fucking locked up here.
Dammit.
I'm coming to get you.
Thank you.
See you around.
Good luck.
Shit!
Just breathe.
They'll be back soon.
Can't...
♪ As a way ♪
♪ We carry on today ♪
♪ And now it's time ♪
♪ For whiskey ♪
We got a chance to...
...get rid
of all these fucking...
...dependents once and for all!
Meet back up here
at the church if...
...it makes an outbreak.
Yeah, these fuckers come
to the buffet,
then we...
torch the fuck out of 'em
by mid-meal.
And that's fucking all of you!
After all this,
that's all you fuckers.
We even...
got that bitch
up in the belfry.
You have to hand it to Lysol.
Fucking, you know,
crazier than a shithouse rat,
but all in all,
he has it pretty good.
Get Doris, boy.
You're gonna tell me
where that fucking coward is?
Just breathe.
- Just breathe.
- Ow!
It's okay. It's okay.
Behind you!
Then there was one.
- Stop!
- Keep fucking around,
I put a bullet right in
her fucking head.
Alan...
We can still undo this.
No, this goes back
so much further than that!
Fucking Sir Lancelot!
Come on!
Come on.
Ah!
You know, Joss,
I wasn't the one who brought
these people here.
I didn't have a chick bringing
plagued-up opies into the flock.
Fuck you!
Alan...
I know how you feel.
There was a time when I wanted
to run that compound down myself.
But these are real people.
Don't you open
that fucking trunk!!
What are youse gonna do to me?
Don't.
Joseph... I've been bit.
Y'know...
when you have some time to sit and
think, you'll thank me.
Set you all free!
Now.
A question... Joseph...
Between brothers.
You really think that... that sick chick
made it in the Muppet house by accident?
Where do you think
I got the idea?
I'm sorry.
Jesus, God, what the fuck
are we gonna do?
We're not gonna die here.
Listen.
- What are we gonna do, swim?!
- Listen!
Where the fuck have you been?
- They wouldn't let me wait. I heard shots, so I came.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Okay. Okay.
It'll be okay. I got you.
Let's go,
let's get the fuck outta here.
You got her?
Come on, breathe. Yeah.
We need to go.
Grandpa... we need to go.
I'm not leaving this land
again.
Don't look back here.
None of you are getting past
this line.
You can do it.
Just push.
Come on, push. Come on, push.
Charlie, you can do this.
You can do this. Push.
Come on, just push, Charlie.
You're almost there.
You don't know
how much this hurts.
I do, I do.
Come on, just push.
- Just push. Just push.
- Alright, yeah. You're gonna have to push.
Otherwise I'm gonna
have to cut you, okay?
You're doing so good, come on.
Push, push.
You're doing really great.
Come on.
Almost there.
It's okay. I love you so much.
Is it too late?
It's a little girl.
The gun?
Do you want to hold her?
No. I've been bitten.
I'm sick, I can feel it.
She can't get sick.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Take her back.
- Charlie, you can hold her.
- No, I don't wanna hurt her. Take her back.
- She's gonna be okay.
- Hmm.
- Maybe you'll be too.
- No, I won't.
Joseph...
we have to end this.
Don't let me turn into one of
those dead people. Look at her.
Hey.
We did it.
Love her.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
@ subs4free.info
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from @ subs4free.info